[Bloster] All right,
how many are there?
[Welfin] Right around 5,000,
and that's only about a fifth
of the quota we're aiming for.
[Bloster] The King
must be pretty ticked off.
He plays so much Gungi
that he barely eats.
only after you get a taste yourself.
I'll do whatever those monsters tell me.
[Welfin] I bet Sir Shaia anticipated
things would turn out like this
when he gave us our abilities.
He gets mad if you call him
by his old name now.
[opening theme music playing]
[singer singing in English]
[singer singing in Japanese]
[Leol] And his abilities?
[Flutter] Much like the others,
he's used only physical attacks thus far.
[Leol] Okay. Just let me know
if he reveals his abilities.
Once Welfin and Bloster arrive,
we'll take care of those figures in white.
[Flutter] Damn!
I lost sight of him.
Sir Leol, it appears that
the man in the suit and glasses
has the ability to teleport.
[narrator] Knov's ability
is called hide-and-seek,
and it does indeed allow him to teleport.
By placing his hand
over a wall or on the ground,
he can open a portal to a Nen dimension.
What's more, he can then
send people or objects
through that portal to the other side.
Hide-and-seek creates a Nen dimension
of 21 rooms spread across four floors.
Each room is completely
independent from the others.
so in order to return
to the real world, one must exit
but exactly how many
depends on the size of the room.
The exit leads directly
back to the portal
that was used for entry,
so as a general rule,
one can only enter and exit
via the location of the entry portal.
However, the master key
in Knov's possession
is able to connect any door
to any portal in any location.
[distant gunfire echoing]
[Knov] No change. All in good order.
[narrator] Morel's Deep Purple
is primarily used for defense.
the figures in white
avoid direct contact with their opponents,
lest they betray their secret.
[dramatic music playing]
[Knov] That's a Chimera.
But what's it doing here?
We're pretty far from the battlefield.
Is it scouting the area?
There were strange dragonflies
around town.
I thought they were a local species,
but could they be products of his Nen?
Seems likely.
If it's a Chimera Ant that
specializes in gathering intel,
I need to neutralize it, and quickly!
[Cheetu] Hey! Hey!
Whoa, there!
I knew you were playing possum
all along.
You can't trick me.
I can't sleep
with all your damn racket!
then you should have enforced rules
that would make people chase you.
Looks like his new ability
still needs some work.
[Morel] He's obsessed with
challenging me to a footrace.
Between that and
his constant need for attention,
Look! I'm over here! Don't you
wanna get up and grab me?
[Morel] Now it's just a waiting game.
As soon as he gives up
and steps away from me,
I win.
[thunder rumbling]
[Champion] Mortar, two-seven-two.
Fort, seven-one-two. Your move.
All right then. Prince, one-six-two.
[Champion] Captain, three-two-two.
I'm finished.
Her opening array is just as I expected.
She's moving toward my King
while staying in wing formation.
Now let us begin to play the game.
[King] Her first move
will be to position her archer
on her right flank
to threaten a trident attack,
but shifting her pieces to the right
exposes her left flank to attack.
This time, I will disrupt your rhythm.
[Champion] Cavalry, two-nine-one.
[King] Her trident attack and
the movement of her left flank
but instead, I'll do this!
Duke, five-five-one.
[Shaiapouf] She had been
playing with a consistent tempo,
but now she's paused
for the first time.
[King] When attacking
from this central placement,
the possibilities are infinite.
There are no correct moves.
gasp for air!
[ominous music playing]
[Champion] New duke,
nine-two-one.
[King gasps]
[dramatic music playing]
[King] I resign.
You knew that this was
a dead end, didn't you?
Yes.
Then why did you pause to
think before making your move?
You could have made it immediately.
[Shaiapouf] The King has moved
this match off the board.
A wrong answer could mean her death.
[thunder rumbling]
Actually sir,
this "detached castling" strategy
you were using is more commonly
known as "Kokoriko."
is also my novelty move,
called "Central duke."
At the time, they both
drew a lot of attention.
The sequence from "Kokoriko"
to "Central duke"
was an excellent way to test
each other's level of insight.
It was very popular.
I was so happy that a fool
like me could still give birth
to something that was so intelligent.
I even called it "My smart little baby."
But soon after that,
I found out how to kill it.
A year after I came up with "Kokoriko,"
an opponent used it against me
in the national title tournament,
and I figured out this countermove,
so I was able to win the match.
But then it disappeared.
You didn't see it in any more matches,
or even in textbooks.
To think that you came up
with the same strategy I had,
I was so honored and touched,
so much so that my heart trembled.
It felt like…
seeing my dead baby come back to life.
That's how it felt.
[King scoffs]
Rubbish.
I've lost interest. Take a break.
[Champion] Huh?
-[King] Once we begin again--
-[Champion] Eh?
[Shaiapouf]
I'm actually impressed.
The King has never
listened to someone else
for that long before, not nearly.
Oh, well. It should
have no significance.
[Morel] Four hours have passed?
That guy's way too predictable.
Wait. It's only half done.
[laughs]
Not getting anxious, are you?
[Morel] Didn't you notice?
It's not time to begin.
It's already over.
Just take a look at your ankle.
[Cheetu] Huh?
I had to go all the way around
so you wouldn't notice what I was doing.
It turned to a pretty long rope.
[Cheetu gasps]
Won't be long now.
[Cheetu growls]
[laughs]
Guess it's your turn to try
whatever you can think of,
but don't expect it to work.
[Cheetu gasps]
[groans]
Don't underestimate
the power of smoke.
This rope's essentially unbreakable.
Struggle all you want.
[Cheetu growling]
This is a game of tag,
so he won't attack me.
All I have to do is touch his body,
and it'll terminate his ability.
He's the one who chose for
this game to last eight hours,
even though he doesn't have
the attention span for it.
I'm not your enemy here.
but now that he finds himself cornered
with nowhere to run and nowhere to hide…
Huh?
[narrator] He creates a new ability.
[dramatic music playing]
A crossbow and claws?
[Cheetu chuckles]
[Morel] Something for both close-range
and long-range combat.
[laughs]
Thanks a lot!
You just helped me gain
an awesome new ability!
See? Got any idea what it is?
There!
Why don't you
try out those claws already?
It'll save me the trouble
of walking over there.
I'll tell you why
you're gonna lose, because…
[laughs]
Come on! Just die,
so tagging me won't matter!
Huh? This feels like…
While you read your manga
and cackled to yourself,
My copy went one way,
and I went the other.
Sleeping doesn't mean
the fight just stops.
You really should have
kept your eyes on me.
Well? Still wanna fight?
Maybe you'd be willing
to fill me in on a little something, then.
Would you mind telling me
what would have happened
if I hadn't caught you back there,
or do you know?
[Cheetu] It doesn't matter anymore.
Once I've been caught,
I can't use that ability ever again.
[laughs] Oh, it's no big deal.
I'll just ask Sir Shaia for a new ability!
I won't lose next time!
Just you wait!
[Morel] All right, then.
So his superior is most likely
a royal guard named Shaia,
[cell phone rings]
[Knov] Let's meet. We'll talk inside.
[Leol] Flutter, come in!
I can't ever lose face
in front of Pitou.
Well, we're gonna head back, then.
[Leol] Wait.
Hold on a second. It's fine.
I think I can handle it.
At least you're both trustworthy.
Idiots. As if I'd tell you the truth.
[narrator]
This is Leol's rental pod.
It's a device that allows him
to temporarily borrow
before he can put it into action.
First, he must have seen the ability,
or at the very least know its name.
SATELLITE DRAGONFLIES
Second, he must grant the target a favor
and confirm by saying, "You owe me,"
or, "This isn't free,"
something along those lines.
And the target
must respond affirmatively,
[Leol] Flutter's fine.
[Welfin chuckles]
[Leol] He's not responding,
because he's either unconscious,
or too far away.
[narrator] A rental
can be used for one hour.
During the rental period,
the target cannot use
the borrowed power.
[Leol] He's still alive, anyway.
Looks like we can stay in touch.
[Bloster] All right. We'll keep
the weaklings at a distance
while you deal with that one.
not until I make the King owe me one.
[narrator] Taking the ticket
and ripping it up activates the ability.
[Leol] They're here.
Time to start scouting.
[thunder rumbling]
[King] I don't like it.
During our matches, my rhythm
is the one being disrupted, not hers.
By all rights, this should be
an unbearable indignity,
and yet, although
I find myself frustrated,
I enjoy it at the same time.
[closing theme music playing]
What I don't understand…
is why.
[singer singing in Japanese]
-[Morel] Well…
-[Gon gulps]
[Morel] Tonkotsu.
[singer singing in Japanese]